A Guide to the Records of William James McKeefery, Vice President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1969-1973
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Williams Hall incidents Cases D-F. (Box-folder 12-450)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases G-J. (Box-folder 12-451)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases K-M File 1 of 2. (Box-folder 12-452)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases K-M File 2 of 2. (Box-folder 12-453)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases N-R. (Box-folder 12-454)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases S-V. (Box-folder 12-455)
- Williams Hall incidents Cases W-Z. (Box-folder 12-456)
- Unrest, Spring 1970. (Box-folder 12-457)
- Trip Abroad. (Box-folder 12-458)
- YMCA. (Box-folder 12-459)
- Business, College of Dean H. H. Mitchell. (Box-folder 13-460)
- Accounting. (Box-folder 13-461)
- Business Administration. (Box-folder 13-462)
- Economics. (Box-folder 13-463)
- Statistics - Dr. Boyd Harshbarger. (Box-folder 13-464)
- Proposal Offering the Doctor of Education Degree. (Box-folder 13-465)
- Education, College of Dean Karl T. Hereford. (Box-folder 13-466)
- College of Education - Dr. Karl T. Hereford, Dean. (Box-folder 13-467)
- Engineering, College of Dean Paul E. Torgersen File 1 of 2. (Box-folder 13-468)
- Engineering, College of Dean Paul E. Torgersen File 2 of 2. (Box-folder 13-469)
- Aerospace Engineering. (Box-folder 13-470)
- Chemical Engineering. (Box-folder 13-471)
- Civil Engineering. (Box-folder 13-472)
- Electrical Engineering - Dr. William A. Blackwell. (Box-folder 13-473)
- Engineering Mechanics - Dr. Dan Frederick. (Box-folder 13-474)
- Mechanical Engineering. (Box-folder 13-475)
- Industrial Engineering - Dr. Marvin H. Agee (Acting). (Box-folder 13-476)
- Mining Engineering. (Box-folder 13-477)
- Water Resources Research Center William R. Walker, Director. (Box-folder 13-478)
- Graduate School - Dean Fred W. Bull. (Box-folder 13-479)
- Home Economics College of, Dean Laura Jane Harper. (Box-folder 13-480)
- Clothing, Textile, and Related Art. (Box-folder 13-481)
- Extension, Division of Dean William E. Skelton. (Box-folder 13-482)
- Research, Division of Dean Randal M. Robertson. (Box-folder 13-483)
- A proposal to consolidate bachelors Programs in Education. (Box-folder 13-484)
- A proposal to consolidate Masters Degree Programs and Program Designations in Education. (Box-folder 13-485)
- Proposal for the Creation of A New Curriculum in the College of Engineering. (Box-folder 13-486)
- Proposal Offering the Doctor of Education Degree Part 1. (Box-folder 13-487)
- Proposal Offering the Doctor of Education Degree Part 2. (Box-folder 13-488)
- Proposal Offering the Doctor of Education Degree Part 2b. (Box-folder 13-489)
- Computer Science And Applications Master of Science Program Proposal. (Box-folder 13-490)
- Proposal for Doctor of Philosophy Degree with an option in education research and evaluation. (Box-folder 13-491)
- Consolidating and Extending Graduate Studies in Education at Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Part 1. (Box-folder 13-492)
- Consolidating and Extending Graduate Studies in Education at Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Part 2. (Box-folder 13-493)
- University Research Associates File 1 of 2. (Box-folder 13-494)
- University Research Associates File 2 of 2. (Box-folder 13-495)
- University Council Committee Construction Revision. (Box-folder 13-496)
- University Needs Meeting With Chief Admin. April 1. (Box-folder 13-497)
- Upward Bound. (Box-folder 13-498)
- Visitation Policies. (Box-folder 13-499)
- Visiting Scholars. (Box-folder 13-500)
- VPI Facilities Inc. (Box-folder 13-501)
- YMCA. (Box-folder 13-502)
- National Association State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) - URA Meetings Nov. 21-23 (Box-folder 13-503)
- Shanks After Hours Raid Appeal to Judicial Committee. (Box-folder 13-504)
- Alling, G.C. (Box-folder 13-505)
- Armitage, J.L. (Box-folder 13-506)
- Reglim, W.R. (Box-folder 13-507)
- Beville, D.C. (Box-folder 13-508)
- Bolecer, W.R. (Box-folder 13-509)
- Brown, D.E. (Box-folder 13-510)
- Brune, E.E. (Box-folder 13-511)
- Burton, M.H. (Box-folder 13-512)
- Cashav, J.G. (Box-folder 13-513)
- Criscione, G.S. (Box-folder 13-514)
- DunRun, R.C. (Box-folder 13-515)
- Duud, G.A. (Box-folder 13-516)
- Embrey, G.W. (Box-folder 13-517)
- Estes, T.N. (Box-folder 13-518)
- Fletcher, M.A. (Box-folder 13-519)
- Gaines, S.D. (Box-folder 14-520)
- Joe, D.D. (Box-folder 14-521)
- Grost, H.W. (Box-folder 14-522)
- Kelley, L.A. (Box-folder 14-523)
- Love, J.M. (Box-folder 14-524)
- Miyamato, G.T. (Box-folder 14-525)
- Orr, M.L. (Box-folder 14-526)
- Ross, H.D. (Box-folder 14-527)
- Salas, G.J. (Box-folder 14-528)
- Sanderson, J.S. (Box-folder 14-529)
- Thompson, R.S. (Box-folder 14-530)
- Watson, P.S. (Box-folder 14-531)
- New Orleans - Burlington Trip. (Box-folder 14-532)
- Admissions. (Box-folder 14-533)
- Men & Women's Program. (Box-folder 14-534)
- Student Services - Dean J. Gordon Brown. (Box-folder 14-535)
- Agricultural Engineering. (Box-folder 14-536)
- Agriculture, College of. (Box-folder 14-537)
- Agronomy. (Box-folder 14-538)
- Animal Science - Dr. Milton B. Wise. (Box-folder 14-539)
- Agricultural Economics - Dr. J. Edwin Faris. (Box-folder 14-540)
- Dairy Science - Dr. R.G. Cragle. (Box-folder 14-541)
- Entomology. (Box-folder 14-542)
- Food Science & Technology - Dr. E. Weal Boyd. (Box-folder 14-543)
- Forestry & Wildlife Conservation. (Box-folder 14-544)
- Horticulture. (Box-folder 14-545)
- Plant Pathology & Physiology - Dr. Houston Couch. (Box-folder 14-546)
- Poultry Science. (Box-folder 14-547)
- Veterinary Science - Dr. Douglas Watson. (Box-folder 14-548)
- Architecture, College of - Dean Charles Burchard. (Box-folder 14-549)
- Arts & Sciences, College of - Dean William Harvard. (Box-folder 14-550)
- Army ROTC - Colonel Earl C. Acuff. (Box-folder 14-551)
- Biochemistry & Nutrition - Dr. Bruce Anderson. (Box-folder 14-552)
- Biology. (Box-folder 14-553)
- Chemistry - Dr. Alan F. Clifford. (Box-folder 14-554)
- Computer Science - Dr. George Gorsline. (Box-folder 14-555)
- English. (Box-folder 14-556)
- Geological Sciences - Dr. Byron N. Cooper. (Box-folder 14-557)
- Health & Physical Ed. (Box-folder 14-558)
- History. (Box-folder 14-559)
- Mathematics. (Box-folder 14-560)
- Performing Arts & Communication - Dr. Paul Distler. (Box-folder 14-561)
- Philosophy & Religion - Dr. Norman Grover. (Box-folder 14-562)
- Physics. (Box-folder 14-563)
- Political Science - Dr. James Herndon. (Box-folder 14-564)
- Sociology - Dr. Gordon Erickson. (Box-folder 14-565)
- Statistics. (Box-folder 14-566)
- Accreditation for Business Part 1. (Box-folder 14-567)
- Accreditation for Business Part 2. (Box-folder 14-568)
- Accreditation for Business Part 3. (Box-folder 14-569)
- Accreditation for Business Part 4. (Box-folder 14-570)
- Dr. Hahn Discussion Topics Part 1. (Box-folder 14-571)
- Dr. Hahn Discussion Topics Part 2. (Box-folder 14-572)
- Dr. Hahn - Current Discussion. (Box-folder 14-573)
- December 1971. (Box-folder 14-574)
- November 1971. (Box-folder 14-575)
- October 1971. (Box-folder 14-576)
- September 1971. (Box-folder 15-577)
- July 1971. (Box-folder 15-578)
- August 1971. (Box-folder 15-579)
- June 1971. (Box-folder 15-580)
- May 1971. (Box-folder 15-581)
- April 1971. (Box-folder 15-582)
- March 1971. (Box-folder 15-583)
- February 1971. (Box-folder 15-584)
- Hahn T. Marshall Jr. President. (Box-folder 15-585)
- Health, Education, & Welfare. (Box-folder 15-586)
- Higher Education. (Box-folder 15-587)
- Higher Education Act of 1965. (Box-folder 15-588)
- Higher Education Associates - Correspondence. (Box-folder 15-589)
- Honor Court. (Box-folder 15-590)
- Honors Seminar. (Box-folder 15-591)
- Housing. (Box-folder 15-592)
- International Students. (Box-folder 15-593)
- Judicial Committee. (Box-folder 15-594)
- Jury Duty. (Box-folder 15-595)
- Proposed New Degree Programs. (Box-folder 15-596)
- Library. (Box-folder 15-597)
- National Assoc. St. Univ. and Land Grant Colleges. (Box-folder 15-598)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 15-599)
- New Communities. (Box-folder 15-600)
- Information Systems. (Box-folder 15-601)
- Inter. American Institute of Ecology. (Box-folder 15-602)
- R. Gale King, President Class of 1972. (Box-folder 15-603)
- Krebs, Alfred H. (Box-folder 15-604)
- Lavery, William E., VP for Finance. (Box-folder 15-605)
- Learning Resources Center. (Box-folder 15-606)
- Malpass, Leslie F. - VP of Academic Affairs, 1. (Box-folder 15-607)
- Malpass, Leslie F. - VP of Academic Affairs, 2. (Box-folder 15-608)
- McKeefery, William - personal. (Box-folder 16-609)
- Miscellaneous (Box-folder 16-610)
- Mayhew, Lewis B. (Box-folder 16-611)
- Music. (Box-folder 16-612)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 16-613)
- National Association State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC). (Box-folder 16-614)
- New Degree proposals. (Box-folder 16-615)
- ODK Spring Forum. (Box-folder 16-616)
- ODK. (Box-folder 16-617)
- Orientation. (Box-folder 16-618)
- Personal Needs and Requests. (Box-folder 16-619)
- Personnel. (Box-folder 16-620)
- Philippines. (Box-folder 16-621)
- Phi Beta Kappa. (Box-folder 16-622)
- Physical Plant Planning. (Box-folder 16-623)
- Picketing. (Box-folder 16-624)
- Placement Services. (Box-folder 16-625)
- Promotions. (Box-folder 16-626)
- Politowski Hearing. (Box-folder 16-627)
- Radio Club. (Box-folder 16-628)
- Recommendations. (Box-folder 16-629)
- Extra Copies of Task Force Materials. (Box-folder 16-630)
- Task Force. (Box-folder 16-631)
- Research Task Force 1. (Box-folder 16-632)
- Research Task Force 2. (Box-folder 16-633)
- Rotary Club. (Box-folder 16-634)
- Ryland, Walter H., Executive Assistant to the President and general council. (Box-folder 16-635)
- Wage Price Freeze - President Nixon. (Box-folder 16-636)
- Salaries. (Box-folder 16-637)
- Security Division. (Box-folder 16-638)
- Sex Discrimination. (Box-folder 16-639)
- Southern Assoc. of Colleges Georgia Accreditation Team. (Box-folder 16-640)
- Southern Regional Education Board. (Box-folder 16-641)
- Southern Universities. (Box-folder 16-642)
- Space Analysis - University office space. (Box-folder 16-643)
- Space Allocation Meeting. (Box-folder 16-644)
- Space needs and standards. (Box-folder 16-645)
- Space Allocation for Patton Hall. (Box-folder 16-646)
- Accounting - charges to budget. (Box-folder 16-647)
- Academic Professional Development Association. (Box-folder 16-648)
- Administrative Intern Program. (Box-folder 16-649)
- Administrative Conference - March 22, 1971. (Box-folder 16-650)
- Admin. Conf. Transparencies. (Box-folder 16-651)
- (AID) Agency for International Development. (Box-folder 16-652)
- Alumni Association. (Box-folder 16-653)
- American Council on Education. (Box-folder 16-654)
- Announcements. (Box-folder 16-655)
- Annual Report. (Box-folder 16-656)
- Annual Report - Building Committee. (Box-folder 16-657)
- Association of Virginia Colleges. (Box-folder 16-658)
- Associated Clubs. (Box-folder 16-659)
- Athletic Association. (Box-folder 16-660)
- Battelle Development Corporation. (Box-folder 16-661)
- Board of Visitors, July 15. (Box-folder 16-662)
- Board room furnishings. (Box-folder 16-663)
- Board of Visitors. (Box-folder 16-664)
- Blacksburg. (Box-folder 16-665)
- John Boiling. (Box-folder 16-666)
- Budget. (Box-folder 16-667)
- Buildings & Grounds. (Box-folder 16-668)
- Building Committee. (Box-folder 16-669)
- Building Committee 1. (Box-folder 16-670)
- Burruss Hall Auditorium. (Box-folder 16-671)
- Final Drawings Placement Office. (Box-folder 16-672)
- Final Drawings Counseling Center. (Box-folder 16-673)
- Final Drawings Coral Music. (Box-folder 16-674)
- Directional Site Plan. (Box-folder 16-675)
- Business Manager. (Box-folder 16-676)
- Cassell, Stuart K. - VP for administration. (Box-folder 16-677)
- Centennial. (Box-folder 16-678)
- Center for Environmental Services. (Box-folder 16-679)
- Chapel. (Box-folder 16-680)
- Classroom Improvements. (Box-folder 16-681)
- Commencement Committee. (Box-folder 16-682)
- Commission - Faculty Affairs. (Box-folder 16-683)
- Commission - Research and Graduate Studies. (Box-folder 17-684)
- Commission - Student Affairs - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 17-685)
- Commission - Student Affairs - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 17-686)
- Commission - Undergraduation Studies. (Box-folder 17-687)
- Community Colleges. (Box-folder 17-688)
- Computer Center - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 17-689)
- Computer Center - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 17-690)
- Computer Comm. (Box-folder 17-691)
- Computing - Hamblen projects. (Box-folder 17-692)
- Consulting other Universities. (Box-folder 17-693)
- Space Spinoffs. (Box-folder 17-694)
- Speaking Engagements and items. (Box-folder 17-695)
- Squires Student Center. (Box-folder 17-696)
- Staff Meeting #1 Minutes - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 17-697)
- Staff Meeting #1 Minutes - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 17-698)
- Staff Meeting #2 Minutes. (Box-folder 17-699)
- Staff Meeting notes. (Box-folder 17-700)
- State Council of Higher Education 10/1/71 meeting. (Box-folder 17-701)
- State Council for Higher Education. (Box-folder 17-702)
- Statements. (Box-folder 17-703)
- Student - Appeals and Reviews - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 17-704)
- Student - Appeals and Reviews - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 17-705)
- Donald Dougherty Hearing. (Box-folder 17-706)
- Judy Johnson Hearing. (Box-folder 17-707)
- Cathy Wells hearing. (Box-folder 17-708)
- Lottinville, Wayne Michael. (Box-folder 17-709)
- Johnson, Judith Dianne. (Box-folder 17-710)
- Wells, Catherine Lee. (Box-folder 17-711)
- Reams, Fred Layne. (Box-folder 17-712)
- Wiggins, Thomas R. (Box-folder 17-713)
- Students - Scholarships and Loans. (Box-folder 17-714)
- Student Health Services. (Box-folder 17-715)
- Student Government Association - Fred George. (Box-folder 17-716)
- Student Life Policies. (Box-folder 17-717)
- Students - Miscellaeous Part 1. (Box-folder 17-718)
- Students - Miscellaneous Part 2 - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 17-719)
- Students - Miscellaneous Part 2 - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 17-720)
- Student Government Association - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 18-721)
- Student Government Association - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 18-722)
- Surinam. (Box-folder 18-723)
- Technology Assessment Proposal. (Box-folder 18-724)
- Traffic Committee (Box-folder 18-725)
- Travel Out-of-State. (Box-folder 18-726)
- Authorization out of state travel. (Box-folder 18-727)
- University Council. (Box-folder 18-728)
- University Council - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 18-729)
- University Council - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 18-730)
- University Council. (Box-folder 18-731)
- University Council Minutes - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 18-732)
- University Council Minutes - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 18-733)
- Consulting Part 1 - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 18-734)
- Consulting Part 1 - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 18-735)
- Consulting Part 2. (Box-folder 18-736)
- Continuing Education Center. (Box-folder 18-737)
- Cooperative Education. (Box-folder 18-738)
- Corps of Cadets. (Box-folder 18-739)
- Council of Deans. (Box-folder 18-740)
- Council of Presidents. (Box-folder 19-741)
- Counseling Center. (Box-folder 19-742)
- James Dean - VP for Student Affairs - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 19-743)
- James Dean - VP for Student Affairs - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 19-744)
- Dean, James - VP for Student Affairs - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 19-745)
- Dean, James - VP for Student Affairs - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 19-746)
- Dr. James Dean. (Box-folder 19-747)
- Deans of Dept. Chairman. (Box-folder 19-748)
- The Dreyfus teacher scholar grant. (Box-folder 19-749)
- Educational Media. (Box-folder 19-750)
- DSP - 66 forms - Misc. Exchange Visitors. (Box-folder 19-751)
- Edurom. (Box-folder 19-752)
- Enrollment Forecasts. (Box-folder 19-753)
- ESSO Foundations Simulated Department Heads. (Box-folder 19-754)
- Exchange Visitor Program. (Box-folder 19-755)
- Exchange Visitor Program Forms. (Box-folder 19-756)
- Faculty Honors and Recognition. (Box-folder 19-757)
- Faculty Miscellaneous. (Box-folder 19-758)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 19-759)
- File Information. (Box-folder 19-760)
- Financial Aid. (Box-folder 19-761)
- Firearms Control. (Box-folder 19-762)
- Food Services. (Box-folder 19-763)
- Football. (Box-folder 19-764)
- Fraternities and Sororities. (Box-folder 19-765)
- Gay Alliance. (Box-folder 19-7656)
- 4-H. (Box-folder 19-767)
- Governors' Day, October 15 & 16, 1971. (Box-folder 19-768)
- Institutional Research Vol.3 - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 19-769)
- Institutional Research Vol.3 - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 19-770)
- Institutional Research - Folder 1 of 3. (Box-folder 19-771)
- Institutional Research - Folder 2 of 3. (Box-folder 19-772)
- Institutional Research - Folder 3 of 3. (Box-folder 19-773)
- Graduate Committee. (Box-folder 19-774)
- Graduate Studies - Reston. (Box-folder 19-775)
- Graduate School. (Box-folder 19-776)
- Malpass, Leslie F. - VP for academic affairs 1. (Box-folder 19-777)
- Academic Affairs, Malpass 2. (Box-folder 19-778)
- Special Academic Programs - Dr. Donald C. Darnton, Director. (Box-folder 19-779)
- Summer School - Dr. Al Krebs. (Box-folder 19-780)
- Accounting - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 19-781)
- Accounting - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 19-782)
- Administration - S.K. Cassell VP. (Box-folder 19-783)
- Administrative Conference, September 14, 1971. (Box-folder 19-784)
- Administrative Intern Program. (Box-folder 19-785)
- Admissions Office. (Box-folder 19-786)
- Affirmative Action. (Box-folder 19-787)
- Alumni Association. (Box-folder 19-788)
- American Association University Professors (Box-folder 19-789)
- American Association University Administration. (Box-folder 19-790)
- American Association Of Higher Education. (Box-folder 19-791)
- American Council on Education. (Box-folder 20-792)
- American Council on Education Publications. (Box-folder 20-793)
- Associated Clubs. (Box-folder 20-794)
- Athletic Association. (Box-folder 20-795)
- Bateman resolution and reports. (Box-folder 20-796)
- Blacksburg, town of William Cook, manager. (Box-folder 20-797)
- Black Study Report. (Box-folder 20-798)
- Board of Visitors. (Box-folder 20-799)
- Boiling, John C. (Box-folder 20-800)
- Building Committee. (Box-folder 20-801)
- Counseling Center. (Box-folder 20-802)
- Corps of Cadets. (Box-folder 20-803)
- Cooperative Education. (Box-folder 20-804)
- Continuing Education Center - Donaldson Brown. (Box-folder 20-805)
- Consulting, January - March. (Box-folder 20-806)
- Consulting, March - May. (Box-folder 20-807)
- Consulting, May - August. (Box-folder 20-808)
- Consulting forms, etc. (Box-folder 20-809)
- Confidentiality of records. (Box-folder 20-810)
- Computing Center. (Box-folder 20-811)
- Computing Center Logs. (Box-folder 20-812)
- Computer Comm. (Box-folder 20-813)
- Community Colleges. (Box-folder 20-814)
- Commission on Student Affairs 1. (Box-folder 20-815)
- Commission on Student Affairs 2. (Box-folder 20-816)
- Commission on Student Affairs, March 1972. (Box-folder 20-817)
- Commission on Research and Graduate Studies. (Box-folder 20-818)
- Commission on Faculty Affairs. (Box-folder 20-819)
- Commencement Comm. (Box-folder 20-820)
- Centennial. (Box-folder 20-821)
- Budget. (Box-folder 20-822)
- Deans. (Box-folder 20-823)
- Degree Offering. (Box-folder 20-824)
- Development University Dr. Wilson Bell, Director. (Box-folder 20-825)
- Discipline. (Box-folder 20-826)
- Education, Sec. of, Earl J. Shiflet. (Box-folder 20-827)
- Educational testing service. (Box-folder 20-828)
- Educational Forum, October 11-12. (Box-folder 20-829)
- EDUCOM (Box-folder 20-830)
- Enrollment. (Box-folder 20-831)
- Eric News. (Box-folder 20-832)
- ESSO Foundation Grant Study Simulated Dept. Head. (Box-folder 20-833)
- Excellence in Teaching. (Box-folder 20-834)
- Faculty Senate. (Box-folder 20-835)
- Federal Communication Comm. (Box-folder 20-836)
- Files. (Box-folder 20-837)
- Finance, William Lavery. (Box-folder 20-838)
- Football. (Box-folder 20-839)
- Foreign Students, Jim Malone, Advisor. (Box-folder 20-840)
- Fraternity/Sorority program. (Box-folder 20-841)
- General Electric Incentive Award. (Box-folder 20-842)
- Governor. (Box-folder 20-843)
- Governor's Day. (Box-folder 20-844)
- Graduate Assembly. (Box-folder 20-845)
- TMH - Returned Memos. (Box-folder 20-846)
- Returned Correspondence, January - April. (Box-folder 21-847)
- TMH, December 1972. (Box-folder 21-848)
- TMH, December 1972. (Box-folder 21-849)
- TMH, November 1972. (Box-folder 21-850)
- TMH, November 1972. (Box-folder 21-851)
- TMH, October 1972. (Box-folder 21-852)
- TMH, October 1972. (Box-folder 21-853)
- TMH, September. (Box-folder 21-854)
- TMH, September. (Box-folder 21-855)
- TMH, August. (Box-folder 21-856)
- TMH, August. (Box-folder 21-857)
- TMH, July. (Box-folder 21-858)
- TMH, June. (Box-folder 21-859)
- TMH, June 1972. (Box-folder 21-860)
- TMH, memos, May. (Box-folder 21-861)
- TMH, Correspondence from May 2, 1972. (Box-folder 21-862)
- TMH, April 1972. (Box-folder 21-863)
- TMH, March 1972. (Box-folder 21-864)
- TMH, February. (Box-folder 21-865)
- TMH, January 1972. (Box-folder 21-866)
- Cable television. (Box-folder 21-867)
- Honor Court. (Box-folder 21-868)
- Housing - Blacksburg. (Box-folder 21-869)
- Housing on Campus. (Box-folder 21-870)
- Information Services - Warren H. Strother, Director. (Box-folder 21-871)
- Industry Center. (Box-folder 21-872)
- Innovations. (Box-folder 21-873)
- Office of Institutional Research - General. (Box-folder 21-874)
- O.I.R. Reports Folder2 - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 21-875)
- O.I.R. Reports Folder2 - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 21-876)
- O.I.R. Reports Folder 2. (Box-folder 21-877)
- Institutional Membership. (Box-folder 21-878)
- International Program Committee. (Box-folder 21-879)
- Judicial Committee. (Box-folder 21-880)
- Kere Kes Appeal (Marie G). (Box-folder 21-881)
- Learning Resources Center. (Box-folder 21-882)
- Library. (Box-folder 21-883)
- Management Information Systems. (Box-folder 21-884)
- Music. (Box-folder 21-885)
- National Association State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC). (Box-folder 21-886)
- National Science Foundation. (Box-folder 21-887)
- Patents. (Box-folder 21-888)
- Peer Institutions. (Box-folder 21-889)
- Personnel. (Box-folder 21-890)
- Phi Delta Kappa. (Box-folder 21-891)
- Philippines. (Box-folder 22-892)
- Placement. (Box-folder 22-893)
- Personnel Division of Students. (Box-folder 22-894)
- Poly Scientific. (Box-folder 22-895)
- Post Secondary Education Office of Education. (Box-folder 22-896)
- Promotions. (Box-folder 22-897)
- Promotions and Tenure. (Box-folder 22-898)
- Purchasing. (Box-folder 22-899)
- Registrar - Registration Payment E. Keller, registrar. (Box-folder 22-900)
- Religious Affairs, Al Payne. (Box-folder 22-901)
- Rescue Squad. (Box-folder 22-902)
- Research Division, Randal Robertson. (Box-folder 22-903)
- Reston. (Box-folder 22-904)
- Richards, Tom (The Nature Conservatory). (Box-folder 22-905)
- Ryland, Walter H. - Counsel. (Box-folder 22-906)
- Scholarships Student Aid. (Box-folder 22-907)
- Southern Association Land Grant Colleges. (Box-folder 22-908)
- Space. (Box-folder 22-909)
- Squires Student Center. (Box-folder 22-910)
- Staff Meeting. (Box-folder 22-911)
- Statements July - December. (Box-folder 22-912)
- State Council on Higher Education. (Box-folder 22-913)
- Statements, Orders, etc. (Box-folder 22-914)
- Student Constitutional Affairs Board 1 - Folder 1 of 2. (Box-folder 22-915)
- Student Constitutional Affairs Board 1 - Folder 2 of 2. (Box-folder 22-916)
- Student Constitutional Affairs Board 2. (Box-folder 22-917)
- Student Government Association. (Box-folder 22-918)
- Student Health Services. (Box-folder 22-919)
- Student Life Policies. (Box-folder 22-920)
- Student Personnel Division, Dr. James Dean. (Box-folder 22-921)
- James W. Dean, VP for Student Affairs, August. (Box-folder 22-922)